<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Malrugo&#39;s World</title>
    <link>https://malrugos-world.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Malrugo&#39;s World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 13:47:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://malrugos-world.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day -3</title>
      <link>https://malrugos-world.netlify.app/posts/day--3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 13:47:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://malrugos-world.netlify.app/posts/day--3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;hello-hello&#34;&gt;Hello Hello&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog. I am getting ready to embark on quite an intense trip. I mean that in the best way possible.&#xA;Soon I will leave my home country and travel to Ciudad de México for almost 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Living&amp;rdquo; in Mexico is something I&amp;rsquo;ve dreamt about for quite a while. When I was 21, my father took me on a trip to CDMX and it was an amazing, dizzying experience. Mexico is the land of my roots and, despite those roots having been severed both through my family and my personal histories, I feel a strong connection to it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite my nervousness, I truly believe God has a plan and that this is the right time for this trip. I am so, so grateful to God and to those around me for that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are two things in particular I am beyond grateful for. The first is my sobriety. My last drink was February 19 of 2023 and since then, thanks to God and to the program of Alcoholics Anonymous and the amazing people in it, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to stay sober and move towards a new way of living that is immensly better. The second is an amazing girl who lives near CDMX and came into my life this year. She was my Spanish tutor, who became a friend, and then much more than that. Although I want to gush about her, I&amp;rsquo;ll just say that I feel blessed and I&amp;rsquo;m incredibly excited to see her and create new memories together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This blog will be a little time capsule to document my days in Mexico, both for myself and for the people I love.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
